

# **Hoang Quoc Huy**

Senior Product Owner/Product Manager

Date of birth: Sep 9, 1995

Gender: Male

Phone: +

Address: Tay Son street, Dong Da district, Hanoi, Vietnam

Website:

Email:

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Become a valued person that any organization need with proficiency and experience. During the next 2 years, I will accumulate as much as possible the attitudes, skills, knowledge and experience related to a technology company to create my competitive advantage and build up my passion value for future personal and professional growth and development in any organization.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Aug 2021 - Present

#### **VinID - One Mount Group**

Senior Product Owner

Main responsibilities:

- Providing vision and direction to the Agile development team and stakeholders throughout the project and create requirements
- Plan and prioritize product feature backlog and development for the product
- Assess value, develop cases, and prioritize stories, epics and themes to ensure work focuses on those with maximum value that are aligned with product strategy
- Provide backlog management, iteration planning, and elaboration of the user stories
- Lead the planning product release plans and set the expectation for delivery of new functionalities

Sep 2020 - July 2021

#### 24H Tech - 24H Online Advertising Jsc

Product Owner (news mobile app - Tinmoi 24h)

Main responsibilities:

- Strategizing, analysis and presenting ideas to related teams (Development team, Design, Operation team, Marketing teams).
- Defining product features according to user needs.
- Leading the development process.
- Acting as the main point of contact between teams and stakeholders.
- Managing and prioritizing product backlog items.

Recognition and Gains:

- Top 3 mobile app in News and Magazines field in Vietnam (App Annie statistic).
- Average Daily Active Users (DAU): 500.000; Retention Day1, Day 7, Day30: 50%, 33%, 25%; DAU/MAU: 33%, Average time on app: 18 minutes
- Monthly Revenue: 100.000 USD

Jan 2020 - Aug 2020	TH EdTech group Co-founder & Product manager Main responsibilities: - Responsible for the strategy, roadmap for mobile app products related to health and fitness field Work with Tech, Design, Product research to deliver on outcomes Team size: 10 Recognition and Gains: - Over 10.000 installers, purchase rate: 4%, monthly retention:20% Total Revenue: 100 million VND per 2 months
Sep 2018 - Dec 2019	Vietnam Studynow JSC - Topica EdTech Group  Leader of product development team.  Main responsibilities:  Manage business analyst and design team for educational mobile and
	<ul> <li>- Manage business analyst and design team for educational mobile app products.</li> <li>- Partner with Tech, Tester deliver on Appstore and Playstore</li> <li>- Team size: 15</li> <li>Recognition and Gains:</li> <li>- Increasing user's engagement to 30% monthly.</li> </ul>
	<ul> <li>Advertising educational mobile app to student effectively: contribute to a 10% increase in the Monthly Active Users and 1,000,000 installers.</li> <li>Top 10 educational app in Vietnam (App Annie statistic)</li> </ul>
EDUCATION	
Oct 2014 - Jun 2018	Bachelor of Honor Program for Talented Students, Hanoi University of Science - Vietnam National University
ACTIVITIES	
July 2017 - Aug 2018	Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST) Research Intern
July 2016 - Jun 2017	Institute of Biotechnology, Vietnam Academy of Science and Technology Undergraduate Researcher
CERTIFICATIONS	
2018	IELTS 5.5

# **HONORS & AWARDS**

2017

2017	3rd prize in The Student Research Conference at Vietnam University of
	Science

Undergraduate Research Program Certificate at KAIST.

of bioinformatics for identification of genetically variants in *chronic myeloid leukemia* patients. Vietnam Journal of Science and Technology. Mar 10, 2017.

### **SKILLS**

Language	English, Vietnamese
Computer	Word, Excel, Powerpoint Programing: C/C++, Free pascal program.

#### **INTERESTS**

Reading book, sport.

## **REFERENCES**

Mr. Hoang Manh Truong

Director of Project, Vietnam Studynow JSC

Mobile: +(84

#### **PROJECTS**

# Tinmoi 24h App

(9/2020 - Now)

Customer	News reader in Vietnam
Description	This is a mobile app that helps the people update hourly news in all fields
Team size	40
My position	Product owner
My responsibilities	Responsible for developing feature on the app following to roadmap.
Technologies used	Data analysis tools, Research tools.

# PeaceMe App

(1/2020 - 8/2020)

Customer	Americans and Europeans love meditation music
Description	This is a mobile app that helps the people experience lower stress,less anxiety and more restful sleep with our guided meditations
Team size	10
My position	Co-founder & product manager
My responsibilities	Responsible for the strategy, roadmap for mobile app product and marketing
Technologies used	Data analysis tools, digital marketing tools.

# **Ecokids project**

(9/2018 - 12/2019)

Customer	9th and 12th grade Vietnamese students
Description	This is a mobile app that helps the vietnamese students learn online convenient, anytime, anywhere from right on your phone.

Team size	100
My position	Leader of project development and digital marketing teams
My responsibilities	Manage business analyst, design and digital marketing teams
Technologies used	Data analysis tools, business analysis tools, digital marketing tools.